[music]
[музыка]
Soviet and
советская и вроде
didn’t seem to
не
talk, I’ll tell the channel the collective farm
разговаривал скажу канал колхоз
can’t stand it
этого не
voluntary and I
вынесет и меня
do
вообще
n’t even meet him, don’t remember
его не встречал не помнит
you can stand me try
вы меня вынесете попробуйте
[laughter]
[смех]
to talk and
поговорить и
ask questions
вопросы задаешь
now, stupid me, take out
сейчас тупого меня вынеси
two and a half minutes, I’ll tell you, I’m
две с половиной минуты расскажу я тебе
not interested in how much  you will tell me 3
не интересен сколько ты мне будешь 3
I'm interested I
мне интересно
wonder for example the question I wonder
интересно например вопрос интересно
how many minutes you will
сколько сколько минут ты будешь мне
tell me what you will
рассказывать что вы будете мне
tell me and you will
рассказывать и же вы будете мне
tell me that you are not interested in me
рассказывать что я вам неинтересен
let's you want to talk
давайте вы хотите поговорить
you're talking about the button
вы говорите о кнопочка
I want
я хочу
to go out if you don't want
выйти если вы не хотите
let's talk
давайте поговорим
let's
давайте
let's think about it or not I'm just
подумаем того или нет мне просто
wondering if I heard this song or
интересно вообще слышал эту песню или
not
нет
wait
подожди
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
and
а
I checked you listening listening listening I
я проверяла тебя слушаю слушаю слушаю я
didn't turn it on I was wondering that you
не включал мне интересно было что вы
wanted to drift this at all how do you like a song
хотели дрифте этим вообще как тебе песню
about your mega basics you create songs
про ваш мега азов вы создаете песни
negatively
негативно
interesting how  you relate to the fact
интересно как ты относишься к тому что
that yours blew up the Azov people from
вот ваши своих подорвали азовцев это с
your point of view  and from the point of view of
вашей точки зрения с точки зрения
ukraine, then sew up when the point of
украины то зашивать же когда точка
view russia committed kazan and on and on the
зрения россия совершила казани и по и на
prisoners
пленных
[music]
[музыка]
found fragments
нашли обломки
fragments
обломки
showed ukraine
показали украины
two where they showed these fragments on the
двоих где показали эти обломки на
bench really lay and put on the
скамейке правда лежали и положили на
bench from fotolia i can
скамейке из fotolia я могу сказать
honestly say i looked through the news  for the launch
честно я просмотрела новости за запуск
for yesterday and more until
за вчерашний день и больше пока не если
you if you remember yes what the
ты если ты помнишь да что показали
wreckage showed him or 100 where they were shown
обломки him or 100 где их показали на
what they were lying on and
чем они лежали и
shown at the scene of the event but on the
показали на месте события а вот на
bench they laid out this piece and that's what
скамейке их выложили вот кусок и вот что
this sound they showed the victims of the fire well  yes, the
это звук они показали погорельцев ну да
fire victims have a tao thi March green and
погорельцы есть дао тхи мартом грин и
now it will be
сейчас он будет
if you are still levon, if you still have
если вы все-таки же levon случае это
weapons, this is only absolutely true
вооружения есть только абсолютно верно
to Ukraine and America,
до украины и америке дальше абсолютно
then you
верно
supply absolutely correctly, it is absolutely true, yes, the fact
поставляете она абсолютно верно да то
that these weapons are Ukraine, so that
что это оружие есть украины так то что
you showed pieces not  on the spot they
вы показали куски не на месте даже так
didn’t even show it soon they showed pieces somewhere
не показали скоро показали куски где-то
that lie on a bench assembled a
которые лежат на лавочке собраны
red cross pendant a
красный крест кулон
document can someone declared the United States
документ может кто заявил сша
absolutely  about without proof to tell
абсолютно без доказательства говорить
you someone wrote in the chat
вам кто-то написал в чате
just said that the United States recognized where
только что сказала что сша признали где
I said they could I said that these are the positions of the
я сказал смогли я сказал что это позиций
Ukrainian side your position is that
украинской стороны ваша позиция что это
Ukraine fired on the Ukrainian now they
украина обстреляла украинская сейчас
will establish if you allow these
установят если вы допустим это
weapons that
вооружение которые
let's let's go back to the beginning of the
давайте давайте мы вернемся к началу
conflict  this is what I want to hear from everyone
конфликт вот это то что я хочу от всех
why russia attacked
услышать почему россия напала на
so many
столько
talked to a lot of people
поговорил со множеством людей
in any way had to create
по-любому должен был создать какую-то
some kind of general opinion
какое-то общее мнение
based on how much you talked with
исходя из того сколько ты поговорил с
people time is cool period let's say
людьми время круто период скажем так как
how you got an opinion
у тебя мнение сложилось
opinion waiting talking opinion about what I
мнение ждем разговаривал мнение о чем у
have developed well, in general, what is the situation
меня сложилось ну вообще какая ситуация
what is the situation where in the banking sector and
какая ситуация где банковской сфере и
formulate the question correctly you
сформулировать вопрос правильно
talk
разговариваешь
how many there were probably every
сколько их было много наверное каждый
day without friction not every day no streams
день без трения не каждый день не стримы
on it doesn’t matter well you talked with a
на не важно ну ты же разговаривала со
lot of
многим количеством
questions of
вопрос
conversation with  Russians from Russians about
разговора с россиянами от россиян о
situation to situation according to situation with what
ситуации к ситуации по ситуации с чем
with ukraine with  kraina let's say this
с украиной с украина давайте так я скажу
my opinion in conversations with Russians
мое мнение в разговорах с россиянами
from Russians comes across somewhere one out of
из россиян попадается где-то один из
ten the one who is against the war, the
десяти тот который против войны
rest are all drowning for the war for the empire
остальные все топят за войну за империю
that's how you are and
вот как вы и
let's get back to the stove I'm watching
давайте вернемся к печке я вас смотрите
you I now ask you a question to which you
я вам теперь задаю вопрос на который вы
they didn’t answer, I’m looking to convey what started
не ответили ищу передать чего началась
normally, your impressions and he said the
нормально у тебя впечатления и он сказал
answer, let’s now you still
ответ давайте теперь вы у тебя до сих
don’t have a picture and let’s you
пор картинка не сложилось и давайте вы
say how the war between Russia and
скажете с чего началась война россии и
Ukraine began, you have a picture of what
украины у тебя картинка сложилась чего
started
началась
where to start,
с чего начать
I answered you now  answer [ __ ]
я вам ответил теперь вы отвечаете ёб
your mother I tell you again you have
твою мать я тебе еще раз говорю у тебя
a general picture in russia you
общая картина сложилась в россии вы
answer my questions we move on
отвечаете на мои вопросы мы едем дальше
you ask me
вы задаете мне
I answered your
я вам ответил на
question switch if you don’t want to
вопрос переключайтесь если вы не хотите
answer if you are
отвечать если вы
leaving let’s where to start the war
уходишь давайте с чего начать война
russia ukraine
россии украины
clear yet  handed out a stupid
ясный еще раздавали тупорылый
psychological point of view when you
психологической точки зрения когда вы
start to aggressive call names it
начинать агрессировать обзываться это
said you no size
сказал вас нет размер
I look at you again
я вам ещё раз
dava  let me repeat my
смотри давайте я еще раз повторю мое
opinion once again that
мнение сложилось что
it was the one who said that he
это та которая говорила что то ли он
would
станет
now become natural there, he loaded his viewers with
сейчас естественно там своим зрителям
such a stupid head, so I’ll
погрузил он такой тупорылые вот я
specifically now say in Russian our
специально сейчас скажу по русски наш
bars are views, this is just a
бруски это виды вот это как раз
strategy for these Russians
стратегия вот этих россиян так
so as not to take them out  according to arguments from on
чтобы не вывозить по аргументам от по
specific facts, they begin to translate
конкретным факта они начинают переводить
in the game here and such bazaar cattle,
в игре сюда и такой базарные [__] так
so who outshouts whom it doesn’t matter
что кто кого перекричит там уже не важно
what your argument is, but then it
какие у тебя аргумент в но тогда
hides, and when you cold-bloodedly want
прячется а когда ты холоднокровно хочешь
to talk about specific facts,
поговорить по конкретным фактам так у
they explode until we just nobody  it didn’t
них взрывается пока мы лишь никому не
explode, these are the standard tricks
взорвалась вот это стандартные приемчики
there, a couple of pas call names for which she
там пара па обзывайтесь для чего она
calls names in order to sort
обзывает для того чтобы как бы вывести
of unbalance the opponent and he also
соперника из равновесия и он суп тоже
began to aggressively not control
начал агрессировать не контролировать
himself and transfer to this base she screams
себя и перевести в этот база она криках
already there
уже там
these are emotions
это эмоции
if you have a sufficient degree of
если у вас достаточная степень
internal stability  so you just
внутренней устойчивости так вы просто
arut they will be like for and like the women in the
арут они будут как за и как бабы на
market there read on you there it seems to be
базаре там читают на тебя там вроде
calm  you listen listen listen to them like a
спокойно слушаешь слушай слушай их как
doctor to a patient
доктор к пациенту
and she either knocks if she is not strong
и она либо стукается если не сильная
violently
буйно
runs away because we are a little naked and
убегает потому что мы немножко гола а
ours look like a fool if she
наш выглядеть дурой если она будет
only yells yell yell well, she won’t be able to
только орать орать орать ну не сможет
reasoned when for two days when
аргументированно когда двое суток когда
already against the background of screaming 2 people here is the
уже на фоне кричащего 2 человека вот
first  doesn’t look like such a fool, at
первое не выглядит такой дурой по
least Russia works in this regard for us, too, it
нам россия работает в этом плане тоже
finances these predators, always
финансирует вот эти хищник всегда
bloggers like this so that Temari don’t go
блогеров таких так это чтобы не ходили
Ukrainian in the summer, support their own
темари летом украинцем поддерживали свой
inside Russian z contexts,
вот этот внутри российский z контекстах
we also
мы тоже
mean people will look at upton aukro
значит люди посмотрят аптон аукро
loaded there and in short there are ukry  such
нагрузили там а короче там [__] такие
stupid Ugrian fascists, and while these
тупые угры фашисты и тогда как вот эти
people are all sorts of people from the cab at the minimum wage, they
люди это всякие из кабины на минималках
just stapled it somewhere there through
просто скобе его где-то там через
some kind of connection, but it sits and
какие-то связи стала а вот это сидит и
how the cattle are there to repent to swords,
как [__] там быть у каяться к мечей
our task is our task is the psyche, so the
наша задача вот наша задача психику так
conclusions  you are clean, we are cats of his muzzle
выводы ты на чистую мы коты морды его бы
and chateau identifier of the warehouse you are
и chateau идентификатор склада ты с
looking for in such a plowed house in order
поиски в таких пропахал домик для того
to then cool and Russian  russian federation
чтобы потом cool и российскую федерацию
find out terrorism cheap terrorists
вызнай терроризм дешевые террористам
sharks of the russian federation disintegrates
акулы российской федерации распадается
sharks will judge all this radiation
акулы будут суд над всем этим излучением
and
и
plastic si van and strangle ransom jealous and
пластик си ван и душишь выкупа ревнует а
our task is so you know the skin and
наша задача так знай ты кожного и
quiet down and before legally or ate
притихнут и до юридически или поедали
we spoke cold-blooded acrobats plugged the
мы spoke холоднокровно акробаты затыкали
sniper to achieve against the elderly and
снайпер добиться в против пожилым и
you know persuasion podlyuka alvin with putin
знаешь уговорах подлюка алвин с путиным
cold-bloodedly laws his water man
хладнокровно законы свою воду мужик шаян
shayan will not be torn
буде не рвалась
yoga nothing but you subscribe put
йога ничего но вы подписывайтесь ставьте
like directly and masya I will be for a long time
лайк прямо и мася я буду давно